Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1951-1968
Department of Special Collections
- CONGRESSIONAL RECORD - clippings 196589th Congress
  - JANUARY 1967 90th CONGRESS (Box Box 8-16)
    - Press Comment on Rhodesia, by W.L. King, 2/27/67 (Page a 896)
    - Compensation to the Province of Mozambique, a letter from A. Franko Nogueira, Minister of For. Affairs, Port., 2/27/67 (Page A 905)
    - Politics and the Press, Eric Sevareid., 2/28/67 (Page H1867)
    - U.S Presence in Vietnam, in World's Interest Enormously Worthwhile, Denis Warner., 2/28/67 (Page A 943)
    - Postal Salaries Based on Locality are Being Seriously Considered, by Joseph Young, 2/28/67 (Page A953)
    - Why the War on Poverty is Turning into a Rout, an article published in the American Gov't, 2/28/67 (Page A883)
    - Rhodesia, statement by the Council of Chiefs, 3/1/67 (Page A991)
    - Rhodesia: A land of Endless Incongruities, by James Kilpatrick, 3/6/67 (Page A1053)
    - Rhodesia Poses Moral for UThant, by J. Kilpatrick, 3/6/67 (Page A1059)
    - A Year of Trial for Trucking, an address by William G. White, Pres. Consolidated Fr'tways., 3/6/67 (Page A1063)
    - Elbie Jay Explainers Fight the War, Hoppe S.F. Chron., 3/7/67 (Page A1097)
    - K.E.L. Patrick, Face saving expected on Rhodesia, 3/8/67 (Page A11029)
    - Outrated Cries for Sanctions, Even War, Echo in the U.N., Clare Booth Luce., 3/9/67 (Page A1173)
    - Security Council is at Fault over Rhodesian Issue from Rhodesian Commentary, 3/14/67 (Page H2679)
    - The Rope of Tibet, by Thomas, 3//3/67 (Page A1221)
    - Russians Seen Urging on Viet Reds, by D. Lawrence, 3/20/67 (Page A1389)
    - Some Good News at Last, McGrory, 3/20/67 (Page A1385)
    - A Reply to Goldberg on Sanctions, by Lord Graham, 3/20/67 (Page A1397)
    - American Opinion Reacts, Press articles on Rhodesia, 3/20/67 (Page H2981)
    - I am a Tired Housewife, by J.P. Strickland (Mrs.), 3/21/67 (Page A1330)
    - Your Tax Dollars Pay for Built-in Povert y, Don Razey, 3/23/67 (Page A1499)
    - Redwoods to the Sea: A new Philospphy on Conservation (Precluded introduction of Bill by Hon. Don Clausen, 3/23/67 (Page H3318)
    - Statement of the Hon. M.C. Botha (So. Africa), 3/23/67 (Page A1491)
    - Trade with the Reds, an article by Mr. Crocker, S.M., 3/3/67 (Page A1547)
    - Big Spare Parts Build-up for Vietnam, F.S. Bessan, 4/4/67 (Page A1565)
    - I Can't Afford It, letter from Theresa Montara, 4/4/67 (Page A1571)
    - Watch Out America, Richard G. Capen, Copely News, 4/4/67 (Page H3491)
    - U.S. Soviet Confrontati on in Mideast Feared, by Richard Wilson, 4/4/67 (Page A1644)
    - The Delicate Art of Not Running, A. Hoppe, 4/4/67 (Page A1562)
    - Free Enterprise Versus Communism, Chas. Gould, 4/11/67 (Page H3891)
    - Radio Smog, an address by Robert E. Lee, 4/1/67 (Page A1702)
    - Capetown, article by Rev. Daniel Lyons, 4/11/67 (Page A 1719)
    - Great Society Programs offin all Directions, article by Richard Wilson, 4/11/67 (Page A1711)
    - Arthur Hoppe in Russia, 4/11/67 (Page A1705)
    - Senator Brooke- Rev. King Contrast. by Frank Gotleins, 4-6-67 (Box Box 8-17, Page A1636)
    - Army Locks Door on Story...and Reporter, article by B.Krauss, 4-12-67 (Page A1759)
    - HOPPE: An Evening to Remember and The Great Ruin Shortage., 4-14-67 (Page A1832)
    - Report on Rhodesia, D. GARNER, 4-17-67 (Page H4221)
    - The Tariff Walls are Tumbling Down. paper by Ed. WIMMER, 4-17-67 (Page H4223)
    - King Stand on War Holds Element of Tragedy, article, C.T.ROWAN, 4-17-67 (Page A1835)
    - Rhodesia, a letter from Ronald TUCKEY, 4-18-67 (Page A1876)
    - HOPPE: Elbie Jay Picks a Target, 4-24-67 (Page A1984)
    - Hoppe: Will Lurleen Support George?, 5-9-67 (Page A2266)
    - CHAMBERLAIN: article, Good Friend as the Chase Manhattan, 5-9-67 (Page A2275)
    - JUDD: address, We've Feared `Congrontation,' but We HaveHad 12, Stood Up, and Things Got Better-- Not Worse, 5-11-67 (Page A2339)
    - HOPPE: Elbie Jay Makes his Peace., 5-15-67 (Page A2375)
    - Lawrence: The Revolution, 5-22-67 (Page A2493)
    - US Navy Men Say ThanksSouth Africa, 5-24-67 (Page A2578)
    - We can't Fight Air Pollution without the FCC'S Help, 5-25-67 (Page H6328)
    - COURTNEY: letter from Rhodesia, 5-29-67 (Page A2568)
    - Rhodesian Information Office: Press Comment on Rhodesia, 5-29-67 (Page A2663)
    - COPLEY: Decline and Fall?, 6-5-67 (Page A2779)
    - SHERMAN: Chris Point in Africa, 6-5-67 (Page H6612)
    - McHUGH: The American Communists., 6-5-67 (Page A2767)